rapidosearch.com 2007-08-12

# Rapidosearch | Privacy Policy

Rapidosearch.com is firmly committed to maintaining and protecting the privacy of your personal and company information. The terms of this policy apply to Rapidosearch.com and all other Rapidosearch websites. The following privacy policy tells you how information that identifies you personally is used, so that you can make an informed choice about using this website and its services.

Rapidosearch.com does not sell, rent, lease or disclose customer information to third parties unless required by law or unless you provide consent to such a disclosure.

1\. Information Collection Some information, such as the website that referred you to us, your IP address, type of browser used, and navigational information, may be collected automatically as part of the website's operation. This data is compiled in aggregate form in order to better understand user activities. This information is important to us as it enables us to continue to provide services and information of interest to our visitors. Website visitor behaviour information is compiled in aggregate and does not represent individually identifiable information.

On some occasions, such as when you request a website review, estimate for services, technical support, or when you subscribe to newsletters and email publications, we may ask for other information through online forms. The information may include your name, email address, postal address, telephone number, website URL and other personally identifying information. We may also ask other questions from time to time. Remember that providing information is always voluntary. You are free to decline to answer any questions or fill out any forms. By choosing to enter and submit the requested information when prompted, you are consenting to our collection and use of such information for the purpose of providing the services or products to you.

Rapidosearch.com does not use cookies on any of its websites and therefore does not use cookies to collect information or plant traceable files on your computer. Rapidosearch.com cannot accept responsibility for the use of cookies on any third party websites linked to from any Rapidosearch.com website, and does not guarantee the security of any personal information disclosed on those sites.

2\. How We Use Your Information The information Rapidosearch.com collects is used to process your requests, provide customer service, develop products and services, and communicate with you in the form of newsletters and notices (if you give us permission to do so). We reserve the right to disclose your personal information if we are required to do so by law or if we believe that disclosure is reasonably necessary to comply with legal process, respond to claims, or protect the rights, property or safety of our company, employees, customers, or the public.

3\. Retention of Your Information Personal information will not be used or disclosed for purposes other than those for which it was collected, except with your consent or as required or permitted by law. It will be retained only as long as necessary for these purposes or as required by law. Rapidosearch.com will ensure that guidelines and procedures with respect to the retention of personal information are maintained. These guidelines will include minimum and maximum retention periods and will conform to any legislative requirements. Subject to any legislative requirement to retain records, personal information that is no longer required to fulfill the identified purposes will be destroyed, erased, or made anonymous.

5\. Security of Your Personal Information Rapidosearch.com takes the protection of the personal information you provide very seriously. Personal information collected is stored in password-controlled servers with limited access.

Internal data is shared through secured transmissions and maintained in secured databases.

Rapidosearch.com may hire certain outside contractors to perform services on our behalf (such as packaging and shipping). We will only provide those companies the personal information they need to complete the desired service. They are not permitted to use customer information for any other purpose.

Information submitted to Rapidosearch.com may be transferred across national boundaries to or from our staff or contractors in other countries. Rapidosearch.com will only disclose information if required to do so by law, legal process or if in good faith it is deemed necessary for the public interest.
